<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
       <string name="terms_and_conditions_complete">Welcome to crowdSOS!
           The crowdSOS website and service are provided by crowdSOS, Inc. (“crowdSOS”, “we” “us” or “our”).  These terms of service (these “Terms of Service”) govern your (“you,” “your,” or a “user”) access to and use of the [http://www.crowdsos.com] web site and its subdomains (collectively, the “Website”) and any downloadable applications (“Mobile App”) and all services provided by crowdSOS via the Website (collectively, the “Services”).  
The crowdSOS Services enable users to report incidents of crime, lost objects or other occurrences (each such reported incident, an “Incident”) that may occur in a city, neighborhood, locality, or other domain whether in a public or private location, or at an event sponsored by a third party (an organizer who sponsors an event, is an “Organizer”).  crowdSOS collects reports of Incidents (each, an “Incident Report”) submitted by its users and through other sources to create data maps (each, an “Incident Map”) that aggregates Incident Reports by geography and time.  Through our Services, users can be notified of Incidents that have been reported in their area through the crowdSOS Services.  In order to use the crowdSOS Services, a user must have a mobile device enabled with our Mobile App, or through a computer that can access our Website, if we make some Services available through our Website from time to time.  
1.	Acceptance of Terms.  
PLEASE REVIEW THESE TERMS OF SERVICE BEFORE USING THE WEBSITE OR ANY OF THE SERVICES, AS THEY MAY HAVE CHANGED SINCE YOUR LAST VISIT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, THEN DO NOT USE THE WEBSITE OR OUR SERVICES. BY USING OUR WEBSITE OR ANY OF OUR SERVICES, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD AND HEREBY INDICATE YOUR UNCONDITIONAL ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS OF SERVICE.
2.	Scope of Service.  
The crowdSOS Services are in beta form.  We expect our Services will change significantly over time and, as a result, crowdSOS may update these Terms of Service from time to time, effective from each such update. We may alter, suspend, or discontinue our Services in whole or in part, at any time and for any reason, without notice.  The Services may also periodically become unavailable due to maintenance or malfunction of computer equipment or for other reasons you are responsible for obtaining any equipment and Internet service necessary to access our Website and for paying any fees for the equipment and service you select.  
If you use our Mobile App, your mobile carrier’s normal rates and charges apply. We are not responsible for any charges you incur from your mobile carrier as a result of use of the Services.  You are responsible for ensuring that at all times while using the Service you are not in violation of your wireless data service agreement.
3.	The crowdSOS Services are Not for Emergency Reporting.
DO NOT RELY ON OUR SERVICES FOR ANY EMERGENCY COMMUNICATION WHATSOEVER TO LAW ENFORCEMENT OR FIRST RESPONDERS. IN THE EVENT OF AN EMERGENCY, PLEASE DIAL “911” WHERE APPLICABLE OR THE APPROPRIATE EMERGENCY PHONE NUMBER OR OTHER METHOD IN YOUR JURISDICTION. OUR SERVICES ARE OFFERED AS A CONVENIENCE ONLY AND DO NOT OFFER MONITORING, ALARM, OR EMERGENCY NOTIFICATION SERVICES. YOU SHOULD NOT RELY UPON ANY SERVICE PROVIDED BY CROWDSOS IN PLACE OF SUCH LAW ENFORCEMENT OR FIRST RESPONDER SERVICES. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR PROCURING SUCH LAW ENFORCEMENT OR FIRST RESPONDER SERVICES AND CROWDSOS IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR, AND YOU EXPRESSLY, IRREVOCABLY, AND UNCONDITIONALLY RELEASE CROWDSOS FROM, ANY CLAIMS RELATED TO YOUR FAILURE TO INDEPENDENTLY OBTAIN OR USE SUCH LAW ENFORCEMENT OR FIRST RESPONDER SERVICES.   
4.	Access; Registered Users.
a.	Registered Users. Some of our Services may be restricted to members only, including the registration to certain information about retailer deals. In order to become a member, we may ask you to complete a registration form and create a user name and password (“Login Credentials”).  During any such registration, you are required to give truthful contact information (such as name and email address) in accordance with these Terms and Conditions.  You are responsible for protecting your Login Credentials from unauthorized use, and you are responsible for all activity that occurs on your account (including without limitation financial obligations).  You agree to notify us immediately if you believe that your Login Credentials have been or may be used without your permission so that appropriate action can be taken.  We are not responsible for losses or damage caused by your failure to safeguard your Login Credentials. For your convenience as a crowdSOS User, all information that you provide to crowdSOS is subject to crowdSOS \'s Privacy Policy, as may be in effect from time to time. You are responsible for keeping your registration information up to date through your account page, to the extent such feature is made available on our Services. 
	
b.	Social Network Login Credentials. crowdSOS may enable you to connect to your crowdSOS account with your Facebook account, or other third-party social network service provider account information (“Third Party Social Networking Account”) as indicated on our Services from time to time.  By connecting to our Services with a Third Party Social Networking Account, you give us permission to access, store and use your information from such third-party social network service provider including, but not limited to, your user ID, any information that you have permitted the third-party social network service provider to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. Information received by crowdSOS will be subject to our Privacy Policy, but crowdSOS is otherwise not responsible for the information that it receives from such third-party social network service provider. Any such third-party social network service provider accessed from the Services is independent from crowdSOS, and crowdSOS has no control over the terms or content of that web site. Your use of any third-party social network service provider is subject to its term of service and privacy policy. We request that our users exercise caution and good judgment when using third-party social network service providers.  You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on social network service providers and other third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Service.

c.	Acknowledgement to Receive Email.  As a registered user of crowdSOS, you agree to receive emails from us regarding our Services. We may from time to time send you our newsletter with information about upcoming events, or information about our service offerings from us and our partners.  You may opt-out from receiving our newsletter by emailing [unsubscribe@crowdsos.com] or selecting to unsubscribe as may be provided in the applicable e-mail correspondence.

5.	Submitted Content
Any Incident Reports, messages, information, text, images, data, links, or other material submitted by a user, to the crowdSOS Services is referred to herein, individually or collectively, as “Submitted Content.”  You shall own your own Submitted Content.  By submitting such Submitted Content, you hereby grant to crowdSOS an irrevocable, perpetual, sublicensable non-exclusive, worldwide license to copy, review, edit, modify, aggregate, and create derivative works of such Submitted Content, and to distribute, publicly display, perform such Submitted Content, whether modified or not, subject to our Privacy Policy as may be in effect from time to time.   
6.	 Disputes; Release.
crowdSOS expressly disclaims any liability or claims that may arise between you and any other users of our Services. You are solely responsible for your interactions with any other user and any disputes that arise from interactions with any of the foregoing. 
Because crowdSOS is not responsible for the interaction between you and any other users or any related transactions, in the event that you have a dispute with one or more other users, you hereby release crowdSOS (and our officers, directors, agents, investors, subsidiaries, and employees) from any and all claims, demands, or damages (actual or consequential) of every kind, known and unknown arising out of or in any way related with such disputes. 
If you are a California resident, in connection with the above release, you waive California Civil Code Section 1542, which says: "A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which, if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor."
7.	crowdSOS Content.
Subject to these Terms of Service and any other agreement between you and crowdSOS, we hereby grant to you a personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive, non-sublicensable right and license to access and use the Services, and all Content therein, solely within the scope of your status as a user of our Services.  The term “Content” means all information, text, images, data, links, or other material posted on the sections of our Services that are (i) publicly available and (ii) which you have the right to access, whether created by us or provided by a third party for display on our Services.  
We reserve the right to make changes to document names and content, descriptions or specifications of products or services, or other information without obligation to issue any notice of such changes. 
Nothing contained on our Services should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use our Services or any Content displayed on our Services, through the use of framing or otherwise, except: (a) as expressly permitted by these Terms of Service; or (b) with our prior written permission or the permission of such third party that may own the trademark or copyright of material displayed on our Services.
8.	Content Submitted by Users.
a)	Accuracy.  If you choose to provide information to register for or participate in a service, event, or promotion on our Services (including without limitation all Incident Reports that you submit), you agree that you will provide accurate, complete, and up to date information as requested on the screens that collect information from you.  Please refer to our Privacy Policy, as may be in effect fro time to time, for information on our practices for handling personally identifiable information.  
b)	Liability.  We are not responsible or liable for the conduct of users or for views, opinions and statements expressed in Content submitted for display through our Services or Submitted Content.  We do not prescreen Incident Reports or other information submitted to our Services, including without limitation Submitted Content.  With respect to such Content or Submitted Content posted on or through our Services, we act as a passive conduit for such distribution and are not responsible for such Content or Submitted Content.  Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers, or other information in the Services provided by users are those of the respective author(s) or distributor(s) and not of crowdSOS.  We neither endorse nor guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any such Content or Submitted Content.  You are responsible for ensuring that Content and Submitted Content submitted to or through our Services Submitted Content is not provided in violation of any copyright, trade secret or other intellectual property rights of another person or entity or of any applicable law.  You shall be solely liable for any damages resulting from any infringement of copyrights, trade secret, or other intellectual property rights, or any other harm resulting from your uploading, posting, submission or use of Content or Submitted Content to our Services.  
c)	Monitoring.  We have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor Content or Submitted Content submitted or on or through our Services, to determine compliance with these Terms of Service and any other applicable rules that we may establish, from time to time.  We have the right in our sole discretion to edit or remove any Content submitted in connection with our Services.  Without limiting the foregoing, we have the right to remove any material that crowdSOS, in its sole discretion, finds to be in violation of these Terms of Service or otherwise objectionable, and you are solely responsible for the Content and Submitted Content that you post on or through our Services and the manner in which you use Content and our Services.  

9.	Prohibited Conduct. 
By accessing our Services, you agree to abide by the following standards of conduct. You agree that you will not, and will not authorize or facilitate any attempt by another person to use our Services to:

a. 	Transmit any Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, offensive, obscene, pornographic, lewd, lascivious, or otherwise objectionable, as determined by crowdSOS.
b. 	Post Incident Reports or other Submitted Content you know is false, misleading, untruthful, or inaccurate.
c. 	Engage in commercial activities on our Services or using our Services without crowdSOS’s prior approval.
d. 	Promote a business or other commercial venture or event, or otherwise use the Services for commercial purposes, except as expressly permitted by crowdSOS; 
e. 	Use a name or language that crowdSOS, in its sole discretion, deems offensive.
f. 	Post defamatory statements.
g. 	Post hateful or racially or ethnically objectionable Submitted Content.
h. 	Post Submitted Content which infringes another\'s copyright, trademark or trade secret.
i. 	Post unsolicited advertising or unlawfully promote products or services.
j. 	Harass, threaten or intentionally embarrass or cause distress to another person or entity.
k. 	Impersonate another person.
l. 	Promote, solicit, or participate in any multi-level marketing or pyramid schemes.
m. 	Exploit children under 18 years of age.
n. 	Engage in disruptive activity such as sending multiple messages in an effort to monopolize the Services.
q. 	Invade the privacy of any person, including but not limited to posting personally identifying or otherwise private information about a person without their consent (or their parent’s consent in the case of a child under 13 years of age).
r. 	Solicit personal information from children under 13 years of age.
s. 	Violate any federal, state, local, or international law or regulation.
t. 	Encourage conduct that would constitute a criminal or civil offense.

You agree not, and will not permit any person or entity  to: (i) use, or allow the use of, the Services for any unfair or deceptive practices or in contravention of any federal, state, local, foreign, or other applicable law, or rules and regulations of regulatory or administrative organizations; (ii) act in a fraudulent, tortious, malicious, or negligent manner when using the Services; (iii) obtain unauthorized access to any computer system through our Services or the Mobile App; (iv) introduce viruses, worms, Trojan horses and/or harmful code to our Services or the Services; and (v) use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other automated device, process, or means to access, retrieve, scrape, or index any portion of the Service, Submitted Content, or Content.  
  
crowdSOS reserves the right, without prior notice and in its sole discretion, to decide whether your use of the Services violate these Terms of Service for any of the above reasons or for any other reason, and if crowdSOS does so, to remove such content which you post or submit to our Services and/or terminate your access to any Services.
10.	Indemnification.
By using our Services, you agree to indemnify, hold harmless and defend crowdSOS and its officers, directors, employees and agents from any claims, damages, losses, liabilities, and all costs and expenses of defense, including but not limited to, attorneys\' fees, resulting directly or indirectly from a claim by a third party that arises in connection with your Submitted Content and/or use of the Services.  
11.	Intellectual Property Rights.
You agree and acknowledge that the structure, organization, and code used in conjunction with our Services are proprietary to crowdSOS.  You shall not, and shall not permit any person or entity to: (i) use our Services or any Content on a service bureau, time sharing or any similar basis, or for the commercial benefit of any other person or entity; (ii) alter, enhance, or make derivative works of the Services; or (iii) reverse engineer, reverse assemble or decompile, or otherwise attempt to derive source code from, our Services or any software component of the crowdSOS Services.  You shall not sell, transfer, publish, disclose, display or otherwise make available the crowdSOS Services including any modifications, enhancements, derivatives, and other software and materials provided hereunder by crowdSOS or copies thereof to others in violation of these Terms of Service.
Unless otherwise noted, all Content contained on the Services is the property of crowdSOS and/or its affiliates or licensors, and is protected from unauthorized copying and dissemination by United States copyright law, trademark law, international conventions and other intellectual property laws.  Product names are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.   
12.	Copyright Infringement; Notice and Take Down Procedures.
If you believe that any materials on our Services infringe your copyright, you may request that they be removed.  This request must bear a signature (or electronic equivalent) of the copyright holder or an authorized representative and must include the following information:  (1) identification of the copyrighted work that you believe to be infringed, including a description of the work and, where possible, a copy or the location of an authorized version of the work; (2) identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and its location, including a description of the material, its Website location or other pertinent information that will help us to locate the material; (3) your name, address, telephone number, and email address; (4) a statement that you have a good faith belief that the complained of use of the materials is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; (5) a statement that the information in your claim is accurate; and (6) a statement that "under penalty of perjury," you declare that you are the lawful copyright owner or are authorized to act on the owner’s behalf.  Our agent for copyright issues relating to our Services or our Services is: Copyright Agent or copyright@crowdsos.com 
In an effort to protect the rights of copyright owners, we maintain a policy for the termination, in appropriate circumstances, of users of our Services who are repeat infringers.
13.	Links to Third-Party Websites. 
The Services may contain links to non-crowdSOS web sites. These links are provided to you as a convenience, and crowdSOS is not responsible for the content of any linked web site.  Any non- crowdSOS web site accessed from the Services is independent from crowdSOS, and crowdSOS has no control over the content of that web site. In addition, a link to any non- crowdSOS web site does not imply that crowdSOS endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or use of such web site.  Use of any third party site is subject to its term of service and privacy policy. We request that our users exercise caution and good judgment when using third-party web sites.
14.	Disclaimer.
Under no circumstances will we be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information in any Content, Submitted Content, information provided by a user or by your use of our Services.  It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information, opinion, advice or other content available through our Services.  You are responsible for seeking the advice of professionals, as appropriate, regarding the evaluation of any specific information, opinion, advice or other content.

ALL CONTENT, SUBMITTED CONTENT, INCIDENT REPORTS, TEXT, IMAGES, AND OTHER INFORMATION ON OR ACCESSIBLE FROM OUR SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. SPECIFICALLY, BUT WITHOUT LIMITATION, CROWDSOS DOES NOT WARRANT THAT: (i) THE INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON OUR SERVICES IS FREE OF ERRORS; (ii) THE FUNCTIONS OR SERVICES (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO MECHANISMS FOR THE DOWNLOADING AND UPLOADING OF CONTENT) PROVIDED BY THIS SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, SECURE, OR FREE OF ERRORS; (iii) DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR (iv) THIS SERVICES OR THE SERVER(S) THAT MAKES OUR SERVICES AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.

NEITHER CROWDSOS NOR ITS AFFILIATES OR LICENSORS ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONDUCT BETWEEN USERS.  CROWDSOS AND ITS AFFILIATES AND LICENSORS CANNOT AND DO NOT GUARANTEE THAT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION SUPPLIED BY YOU WILL NOT BE MISAPPROPRIATED, INTERCEPTED, DELETED, DESTROYED OR USED BY OTHERS. 

15.	Limitation of Liability. 
	(a)  Disclaimer.  IN NO EVENT SHALL CROWDSOS BE LIABLE TO YOU, ANY OTHER USER OF OUR SERVICES, ORGANIZERS OR ANY OTHER PERSON OR ENTITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF DATA, LOSS OF USE, OR COSTS OF OBTAINING SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES) ARISING OUT OF THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OR MISUSE OF THE SERVICES, SUBMITTED CONTENT, CONTENT OR ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED THEREON, WHETHER BASED UPON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF CROWDSOS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR LOSSES.  
(b)  Limitation.  CROWDSOS\'S AGGREGATE LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING FROM THIS AGREEMENT, CUMULATIVELY, SHALL NOT EXCEED THE GREATER OF (I) $1.00 OR (II) THE AGGREGATE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID TO CROWDSOS FOR THE SERVICES, IF ANY, IN THE THEN-PRIOR TWELVE (12) MONTH PERIOD.
(c)  Waiver of Class Action.  ANY CLAIMS BROUGHT BY YOU OR CROWDSOS MUST BE BROUGHT IN THAT PARTIES’ INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING.  YOU HEREBY WAIVE ANY AND ALL RIGHTS TO BRING ANY CLAIMS RELATED TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICE AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING.
(d)  Exclusions.  SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.  ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.  
16.	Jurisdictional Issues.
We make no representation that information on our Services is appropriate or available for use outside the United States.  Those who choose to access our Services from outside the United States do so on their own initiative and at their own risk and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws.  By using our Services, you consent to having your Personal Information (as defined in our Privacy Policy posted through our Services) transferred to and processed in the United States subject to the restrictions on such data as provided in our Privacy Policy posted through our Services from time to time.  
17.	Termination.  
We may terminate your access to our Services, in our sole discretion, for any reason and at any time, upon electronic notice to you at the e-mail address provided by you at registration.  You agree that we are not liable to you or any third party for any termination of your access to our Services.  For the avoidance of doubt, you acknowledge and agree that, upon termination of these Terms of Service for any reason, you shall immediately pay all amounts that accrued prior to the date of termination, and that any obligation to pay crowdSOS that accrued prior to the termination hereof will survive following such termination.
18.	Unsolicited Ideas and Feedback.
While we welcome your feedback, ideas, and suggestions (collectively, “unsolicited ideas”), it is important to be aware of the following restrictions with regards to unsolicited ideas you provide to us. If you send us feedback, ideas, or suggestions, you agree that: (1) your unsolicited ideas become the property of crowdSOS and you are not owed any compensation or acknowledgment in exchange; (2) none of the unsolicited ideas contain confidential or proprietary information of any third party; (3) crowdSOS may use or redistribute unsolicited ideas for any purpose and in any way; (4) there is no obligation for crowdSOS to review your unsolicited ideas; and (5) crowdSOS has no obligation to keep any unsolicited ideas confidential.
19.	Governing Law; Dispute Resolution.
These Terms of Service shall be governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, USA, excluding: its conflicts of laws principles; the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods; the 1974 Convention on the Limitation Period in the International Sale of Goods; and the Protocol amending the 1974 Convention, done at Vienna April 11, 1980.  All disputes arising out of or relating to these Terms of Service shall be finally resolved by arbitration before a single arbitrator conducted in the English language in Boston, Massachusetts, U.S.A. under the Commercial Arbitration Rules of the American Arbitration Association (AAA). You and crowdSOS shall appoint as sole arbitrator a person mutually agreed by you and crowdSOS or, if you and crowdSOS cannot agree within thirty (30) days of either party’s request for arbitration, such single arbitrator shall be selected by the AAA upon the request of either party.  The parties shall bear equally the cost of the arbitration (except that the prevailing party shall be entitled to an award of reasonable attorneys\' fees incurred in connection with the arbitration in such an amount as may be determined by the arbitrator). All decisions of the arbitrator shall be final and binding on both parties and enforceable in any court of competent jurisdiction. Notwithstanding this, application may be made to any court for a judicial acceptance of the award or order of enforcement. Notwithstanding the foregoing, crowdSOS shall be entitled to seek injunctive relief, security or other equitable remedies from the United States District Court for the District of Massachusetts or any other court of competent jurisdiction.  Under no circumstances shall the arbitrator be authorized to award punitive damages, including but not limited to pursuant to federal or state statutes permitting multiple or punitive awards.
20.	Miscellaneous.  
You may not assign or transfer your rights or obligations under these Terms of Service in whole or in part to any third party without the consent of crowdSOS.  These Terms of Service shall bind and inure to the benefit of the parties to these Terms of Service and their respective successors, permitted transferees, and permitted assigns.  crowdSOS and you are independent contractors and are not partners, joint venturers, agents, employees or representatives of the other party.  These Terms of Service contain the entire understanding of the parties with respect to the transactions and matters contemplated hereby, supersedes all previous communications, understandings and agreements (whether oral or written) other than any click-through or end user license agreement provided by crowdSOS, and cannot be amended except by a writing signed by both parties or by crowdSOS’s posting of an amended version of these Terms of Service on its Website (which shall be effective only prospectively unless you agree to retroactive changes by click through or written agreement).  The headings and captions used in these Terms of Service are used for convenience only and are not to be considered in construing or interpreting these Terms of Service.  If any part of these Terms of Service is held to be unlawful, void, or unenforceable, that part will be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions.  
21.	Minors.
crowdSOS Services are available only to, and may only be used by, individuals who are 18 years and older who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law.  Individuals under the age of 18 can use our Services only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent.  In this case, the parent is responsible for any and all activities of such minor.  
22.	For Additional Information.
If you have any questions about these Terms of Service, please contact us at: 17 Flagg Street, Cambridge, MA 02138 USA or via copyright@crowdsos.com
Copyright © 2013, crowdSOS, Inc. All Rights Reserved. 
</string>
    
</resources>
